<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IIITB-Connects</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="MasterKeyInfo">This feature requires master key authentication provided to authorized users, i.e. clubs and developers. We are working in making this a common feature.\nBear with us..</string>
    <string name="SearchAlertInfo">While looping through questions…search for the keywords of your query. Maybe someone had been as curious as you, earlier. You may find a match. Else, add your query. We\'ll approach it\'s answers ASAP!</string>
    <string name="OTPVerificationInfo">For user verification purposes, we will send an OTP via text message to the phone number you\'ll just fill. Enter the phone number below to receive a 6-digit verification code on.</string>
    <string name="TemplateDesc">Template image should relate to the challenge being added. Adding no image would result in us, adding your club logo as template image for your challenge.\n<b>Click image to change</b></string>
    <string name="AboutUs">team404dev is an aspiring team of enterprising individuals with different values and goals but with a shared holy grail : a world better connected than what we now have.\n\nAspiring minds and hard working individuals are always welcome. We would be more than happy to join hands and work towards a better future.\n\nWe wish for a happier world. </string>
    <string name="ResetPasswordInfo">Forgot your logging in password?  Relax!\nJust type in the email you entered while registering and a password-reset link will be sent to your email.</string>
    <string name="user_id_deleted_info">You were not registered properly or your IIITB-Connects ID has been disabled. Please contact the support team for further information.\nMail us at team404dev@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="userVerificationCheck">For connecting a smooth bridge between you and us, you need to verify the email you just filled.\nClick on the link mentioned there and we are all set!\nIf you are facing any problem, contact us at team404dev@gmail.com</string>
</resources>
